[Music]
good morning quality leaders and agents
at Prudential our mission our big one is
to provide financial freedom and peace
of mind
Prudential could not be where we are
today with a legacy of 94 years have we
not started with this very big wine this
big why has led us to be the number one
insurer in the hearts and minds of our
people and customers number one in the
hearts and minds means that in
everything that we do repair our people
and customers in mind even though our
business has evolved and grown
significantly over 94 years the agency
force remains core to Prudential in
Malaysia and we will continue to be the
most important and valued distribution
channel in our business Prudential and
agency Falls our partners and that means
we continue to support and invest in all
our agents to ensure we grow our
business your business and ensure our
agency force continues to be the most
professional and productive in the
industry we are investing in many
transformational initiatives aimed at
shifting the agency business to the next
level to prepare us for the changes that
are already here the winners will be
those who will and can embrace a change
adapt and respond
Prudential is the market leader to
densho offers you the best opportunity
to grow and succeed how firstly
nurturing culture not only do we have
the best compensation but importantly
Prudential helps you to achieve your
next level of success we have the best
training facilities Pro Business Academy
has been ISO certified for the last 13
years we provide you with technology
tools that make your life and business
easier with Prudential be a highly
professional leader who attracts
productive new agents bill your agency
with support from year one to MDRT
to see ot and even Beauty number two
higher income you can achieve high
income with higher Commission's under
the balanced scorecard individual
scoring we offer the best compensation
our agency incentives covers all
segments from top to middle segments
given equal chance to all with
Prudential we will support you to
capitalize on balanced scorecard to
outperform and achieve higher commission
up to an additional 15% more Commission
certainly a place for you to work a
professional environment for you to
conduct and grow your business number
four bill your legacy without agency
builder contract when you build your
agency your potential you are building
your legacy Prudential is the one and
only company with succession planning
you build on it and you pass it on
and finally piece of my own retirement
Prudential takes care of you for the
long term even during a retirement with
RGB benefits
this is the value and support that
Prudential offers to you how agency
force so let us continue to work to
build a growing and sustainable future
together
[Music]